Hi, and welcome to the small evaluation and validation section.
大家好 欢迎学习这个简短的评估和验证课程
我叫 Luis Serrano 是优达学城的一名讲师
My name is Luis Serrano and I'm an instructor here at Udacity.
在这节课 我们将侧重于两个问题
In this section, we'll focus on two questions.
第一个问题是
The first question is,
我的模型表现如何？
how well is my model doing?
假设我们已经训练了我们的机器学习模型 问题是
So, let's say we've trained our machine learning model and the question is,
该模型效果不错吗？
is this model good or not?
So, we're going to learn metrics to tell us if it is good or not.
我们将学习一些检测指标 判断模型是否效果不错
And the second question is, once we figure that out,
第二个问题是 检测效果后
how do we improve it based on these metrics?
如何根据这些指标改善模型？
Let's dive right in and learn to evaluate,
我们开始学习如何评估
validate, and improve our machine learning models.
验证和改善我们的机器学习模型吧